One day. One planet. Infinite wonder.
Earth: One Amazing Day is a documentary, family,
adventure film directed by Lixin Fan.
An astonishing journey revealing the awesome power of the natural world.
Over the course of one single day, we track the sun from the highest
mountains to the remotest islands to exotic jungles.
Narrator (voice), played by Robert Redford.
Narrator (voice), played by Jackie Chan.
Narrator (voice), played by Lee Je-hoon.
The Day the Earth Stood Still is a 2008 American science fiction film serving as a remake of the 1951 film of
the same name, which, in turn, was based on the 1940 short story "Farewell to the Master".
Directed by Scott Derrickson from a screenplay by David Scarpa, it stars Keanu Reeves as Klaatu, an alien sent to try to change human behavior in an effort to save Earth from
environmental degradation; this version replaces the Cold War–era theme of potential nuclear warfare with the contemporary issue of negative human impact on the environment.
It co-stars Jennifer Connelly, Jaden Smith, John
Cleese, Jon Hamm, and Kathy Bates.
The Day the Earth Stood Still was originally scheduled for release on May 9, 2008, but was released on a
roll-out schedule beginning December 12, 2008, screening in both conventional and IMAX theaters.
It was met with generally negative reviews from critics but was a
financial success, grossing over $233 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of earth, animals, nature.